<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="1|3.5E:17|CoreRPG:4">
	<library>
		<alcoholsofgolarion static="true">
			<categoryname type="string">Items</categoryname>
			<name type="string">alcoholsofgolarion</name>
			<entries>
				<aacommunity>
				  <librarylink type="windowreference">
					<class>referencetext</class>
					<recordname>communityuse</recordname>
				  </librarylink>
				  <name type="string">Community Use Statement</name>
				</aacommunity>
				<ablicense>
				  <librarylink type="windowreference">
					<class>referencetext</class>
					<recordname>license</recordname>
				  </librarylink>
				  <name type="string">Open Gaming License</name>
				</ablicense>
				<item>
					<librarylink type="windowreference">
						<class>reference_list</class>
						<recordname>..</recordname>
					</librarylink>
					<name type="string">Alcohols</name>
					<recordtype type="string">item</recordtype>
				</item>
			</entries>
		</alcoholsofgolarion>
	</library>
	<communityuse>
		<name type="string">Community Use Statement</name>
		<text type="formattedtext">
		  <p>This<i>Fantasy Grounds Module</i> uses trademarks and/or copyrights owned by Paizo Publishing, LLC, which are used under Paizo's Community Use Policy. We are expressly prohibited from charging you to use or access this content. This<i>Fantasy Grounds Module</i> is not published, endorsed, or specifically approved by Paizo Publishing. For more information about Paizo's Community Use Policy, please visit paizo.com/communityuse. For more information about Paizo Publishing and Paizo products, please visit paizo.com.</p>
		</text>
	</communityuse>
	<license>
		<librarylink type="windowreference">
		  <class>referencetextwide</class>
		  <recordname>..</recordname>
		</librarylink>
		<name type="string">Open Gaming License</name>
		<text type="formattedtext">
		  <p>
			<b>Open Game License Version 1.0a</b>
		  </p>
		  <p>The following text is the property of Wizards of the Coast, Inc. and is Copyright 2000 Wizards of the Coast, Inc ("Wizards"). All Rights Reserved.</p>
		  <p>1. Definitions:</p>
		  <list>
			<li>(a) "Contributors" means the copyright and/or trademark owners who have contributed Open Game Content;</li>
			<li>(b) "Derivative Material" means copyrighted material including derivative works and translations (including into other computer languages), potation, modification, correction, addition, extension, upgrade, improvement, compilation, abridgment or other form in which an existing work may be recast, transformed or adapted;</li>
			<li>(c) "Distribute" means to reproduce, license, rent, lease, sell, broadcast, publicly display, transmit or otherwise distribute;</li>
			<li>(d) "Open Game Content" means the game mechanic and includes the methods, procedures, processes and routines to the extent such content does not embody the Product Identity and is an enhancement over the prior art and any additional content clearly identified as Open Game Content by the Contributor, and means any work covered by this License, including translations and derivative works under copyright law, but specifically excludes Product Identity.</li>
			<li>(e) "Product Identity" means product and product line names, logos and identifying marks including trade dress; artifacts, creatures, characters, stories, storylines, plots, thematic elements, dialogue, incidents, language, artwork, symbols, designs, depictions, likenesses, formats, poses, concepts, themes and graphic, photographic and other visual or audio representations; names and descriptions of characters, spells, enchantments, personalities, teams, personas, likenesses and special abilities; places, locations, environments, creatures, equipment, magical or supernatural abilities or effects, logos, symbols, or graphic designs; and any other trademark or registered trademark clearly identified as Product identity by the owner of the Product Identity, and which specifically excludes the Open Game Content;</li>
			<li>(f) "Trademark" means the logos, names, mark, sign, motto, designs that are used by a Contributor to identify itself or its products or the associated products contributed to the Open Game License by the Contributor</li>
			<li>(g) "Use", "Used" or "Using" means to use, Distribute, copy, edit, format, modify, translate and otherwise create Derivative Material of Open Game Content.</li>
			<li>(h) "You" or "Your" means the licensee in terms of this agreement.</li>
		  </list>
		  <p>2. The License: This License applies to any Open Game Content that contains a notice indicating that the Open Game Content may only be Used under and in terms of this License. You must affix such a notice to any Open Game Content that you Use. No terms may be added to or subtracted from this License except as described by the License itself. No other terms or conditions may be applied to any Open Game Content distributed using this License.</p>
		  <p>3. Offer and Acceptance: By Using the Open Game Content You indicate Your acceptance of the terms of this License.</p>
		  <p>4. Grant and Consideration: In consideration for agreeing to use this License, the Contributors grant You a perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free, non-exclusive license with the exact terms of this License to Use, the Open Game Content.</p>
		  <p>5. Representation of Authority to Contribute: If You are contributing original material as Open Game Content, You represent that Your Contributions are Your original creation and/or You have sufficient rights to grant the rights conveyed by this License.</p>
		  <p>6. Notice of License Copyright: You must update the COPYRIGHT NOTICE portion of this License to include the exact text of the COPYRIGHT NOTICE of any Open Game Content You are copying, modifying or distributing, and You must add the title, the copyright date, and the copyright holder's name to the COPYRIGHT NOTICE of any original Open Game Content you Distribute.</p>
		  <p>7. Use of Product Identity: You agree not to Use any Product Identity, including as an indication as to compatibility, except as expressly licensed in another, independent Agreement with the owner of each element of that Product Identity. You agree not to indicate compatibility or co-adaptability with any Trademark or Registered Trademark in conjunction with a work containing Open Game Content except as expressly licensed in another, independent Agreement with the owner of such Trademark or Registered Trademark. The use of any Product Identity in Open Game Content does not constitute a challenge to the ownership of that Product Identity. The owner of any Product Identity used in Open Game Content shall retain all rights, title and interest in and to that Product Identity.</p>
		  <p>8. Identification: If you distribute Open Game Content You must clearly indicate which portions of the work that you are distributing are Open Game Content.</p>
		  <p>9. Updating the License: Wizards or its designated Agents may publish updated versions of this License. You may use any authorized version of this License to copy, modify and distribute any Open Game Content originally distributed under any version of this License.</p>
		  <p>10. Copy of this License: You MUST include a copy of this License with every copy of the Open Game Content You distribute.</p>
		  <p>11. Use of Contributor Credits: You may not market or advertise the Open Game Content using the name of any Contributor unless You have written permission from the Contributor to do so.</p>
		  <p>12. Inability to Comply: If it is impossible for You to comply with any of the terms of this License with respect to some or all of the Open Game Content due to statute, judicial order, or governmental regulation then You may not Use any Open Game Material so affected.</p>
		  <p>13. Termination: This License will terminate automatically if You fail to comply with all terms herein and fail to cure such breach within 30 days of becoming aware of the breach. All sublicenses shall survive the termination of this License.</p>
		  <p>14. Reformation: If any provision of this License is held to be unenforceable, such provision shall be reformed only to the extent necessary to make it enforceable.</p>
		  <p>
			<b>15. COPYRIGHT NOTICE</b>
		  </p>
		  <p>
			<i>Open Game License v 1.0a Copyright 2000, Wizards of the Coast, Inc.</i>
		  </p>
		  <list>
			<li>System Reference Document. Copyright 2000, Wizards of the Coast, Inc.; Authors Jonathan Tweet, Monte Cook, Skip Williams, based on material by E. Gary Gygax and Dave Arneson.</li>
			<li>Adam Heine. (2015). "The Patch Man", Paizo Inc.</li>
			<li>Amanda Hamon et al. (2013). Foreword: I Do Believe in Fairies!. Fey Revisited. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-507-5</li>
			<li>Amber E. Scott. (2012). Pirates of the Inner Sea. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-405-4</li>
			<li>Amber E. Scott. (2014). Seeing Different Horizons. The Slave Trenches of Hakotep. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-592-1</li>
			<li>Brandon Hodge. (2011). Feast of Ravenmoor. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-367-5</li>
			<li>Brian Duckwitz. (2016). Dead Man's Debt. Paizo Inc.</li>
			<li>Chris A. Jackson. (2013). "Stargazer", Paizo Publishing.</li>
			<li>Chris A. Jackson. (2013). Pirate's Honor. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-523-5</li>
			<li>Chris Willrich. (2014). "The Cloak of Belonging", Paizo Publishing, LLC.</li>
			<li>Colin McComb et al. (2010). Gnomes of Golarion. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-223-4</li>
			<li>Colin McComb. (2011). Faiths of Purity. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-314-9</li>
			<li>Crystal Frasier and Richard Pett. (2018). Songbird, Scion, Saboteur. Songbird, Scion, Saboteur. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-64078-025-5</li>
			<li>Dave Gross. (2011). "A Lesson in Taxonomy". Paizo Publishing. ISBN 978-1-60125-394-1</li>
			<li>Dave Gross. (2012). Queen of Thorns. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-463-4</li>
			<li>Elaine Cunningham, Steve Kenson, China Miéville, and Chris Pramas, et al. (2010). Guide to the River Kingdoms. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-203-6</li>
			<li>Elaine Cunningham, with Dave Gross. (2010). Winter Witch. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-286-9</li>
			<li>Graeme Davis and Rob McCreary. (2011). The Thousand Fangs Below. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-276-0</li>
			<li>Greg A. Vaughan. (2010). The Varnhold Vanishing. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-234-0</li>
			<li>Greg A. Vaughan. (2011). NPC Gallery. Night of Frozen Shadows. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-366-8</li>
			<li>Greg A. Vaughan. (2011). Night of Frozen Shadows. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-366-8</li>
			<li>Hal Maclean and Amber E. Scott. (2010). Halflings of Golarion. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-278-4</li>
			<li>Hal Maclean, Colin Moulder-McComb, Jason Nelson, Jonathan Keith, and Hank Woon. (2010). Andoran, Spirit of Liberty. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-205-0</li>
			<li>Howard Andrew Jones. (2011). Plague of Shadows. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-291-3</li>
			<li>Hugh Matthews. (2012). "Krunzle the Quick". Paizo Publishing.</li>
			<li>James Jacobs. (2007). Sandpoint. Burnt Offerings. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-035-3 </li>
			<li>James Jacobs. (February 6, 2012). Toasting Merrymead with Two New Venture-Captains, Paizo Blog.</li>
			<li>Jason Bulmahn. (2007). The Journey Begins (Pathfinder's Journal). The Skinsaw Murders. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-037-7</li>
			<li>Jason Nelson, Patrick Renie, and David N. Ross. (2014). Alchemy Manual. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-605-8</li>
			<li>Jason Nelson. (2010). War of the River Kings. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-252-4</li>
			<li>Jenny Jarzabski. (2018). In the Grandmaster's Name. Paizo Inc.</li>
			<li>Jesse Benner, Richard Pett, F. Wesley Schneider. (2012). The Life of a Pirate. The Wormwood Mutiny. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-404-7</li>
			<li>Jim Zub. (2012). "Dark Waters Rising" Chapter 1. Pathfinder, Volume 1 #1. Dynamite Entertainment.</li>
			<li>Jim Zub. (2014). "City of Secrets" Chapter 2. Pathfinder:City of Secrets, Volume 1 #2. Dynamite Entertainment.</li>
			<li>Jim Zub. (2014). "City of Secrets" Chapter 3. Pathfinder:City of Secrets, Volume 1 #3. Dynamite Entertainment.</li>
			<li>John Compton, Crystal Frasier, Ron Lundeen, and Todd Stewart. (2019). Concordance of Rivals. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-64078-127-6</li>
			<li>John Compton, et al. (2018). Merchant's Manifest. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-64078-026-2</li>
			<li>John Ling et al. (2013). Magical Marketplace. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-600-3</li>
			<li>Kate Baker, Eleanor Ferron, Michelle Jones, Jason Keeley, Luis Loza, Jacob W. Michaels, Joe Pasini, and David N. Ross. (2018). Inner Sea Taverns. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-64078-016-3</li>
			<li>Keith Baker. (2009). Blood of Dragonscar. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-170-1</li>
			<li>Kevin Andrew Murphy. (2012). "Thieves Vinegar". Paizo Publishing. ISBN 978-1-60125-642-3</li>
			<li>Lucien Soulban. (2011-2012). "Fingers of Death-No, Doom!". Paizo Publishing.</li>
			<li>Mark Moreland. (2017). Taldor, the First Empire. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-999-8</li>
			<li>Matt Goodall et al. (2014). Plunder &amp; Peril. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-680-5</li>
			<li>Matt Goodall. (2011). Cult of the Ebon Destroyers. Paizo Publishing, LLC.</li>
			<li>Michael Kortes. (2011). Ravengro. The Haunting of Harrowstone. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-308-8</li>
			<li>Mike Ferguson. (2010). Pitax. Guide to the River Kingdoms. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-203-6</li>
			<li>Mike Ferguson. (2010). Pitax. War of the River Kings. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-252-4</li>
			<li>Mike McArtor. (2008). Guide to Korvosa. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-078-0</li>
			<li>Mike Shel. (2012). Isles of the Shackles. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-408-5</li>
			<li>Mike Shel. (2013). Irrisen, Land of Eternal Winter. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-486-3</li>
			<li>Neal F. Litherland. (2013). "The Irregulars", Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-631-7</li>
			<li>Neil Spicer. (2010). Blood for Blood. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-251-7</li>
			<li>Neil Spicer. (2010). Realm of the Fellnight Queen. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-224-1</li>
			<li>Neil Spicer. (2011). Ashes at Dawn. Ashes at Dawn. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-312-5</li>
			<li>Neil Spicer. (2014). Torch. Fires of Creation. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-673-7</li>
			<li>Nicolas Logue. (2008). Bugbear. Classic Monsters Revisited. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-079-7</li>
			<li>Richard Pett. (2014). Tephu, City of the Reed People. Shifting Sands. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-590-7</li>
			<li>Rob McCreary. (2009). Ilizmagorti. Cities of Golarion. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-200-5</li>
			<li>Rob McCreary. (2013). The Snows of Summer. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-492-4</li>
			<li>Robin D. Laws. (2012). Blood of the City. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-456-6</li>
			<li>Ron Lundeen. (2014). Iadenveigh. The Choking Tower. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-688-1</li>
			<li>Ron Lundeen. (2016). Hell Comes to Westcrown. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-851-9</li>
			<li>Russ Taylor. (2012). Stone Giant. Giants Revisited. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-412-2</li>
			<li>Stephanie Lorée. (2014). "Armored", Paizo Inc.</li>
			<li>Stephen S. Greer &amp; Amber E. Scott. (2009). Dark Markets: A Guide to Katapesh. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-166-4</li>
			<li>Tim Hitchcock. (2011). Broken Moon. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-310-1</li>
			<li>Tim Pratt. (2014). Reign of Stars. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-660-7</li>
			<li>Tim Pratt. (2015). Liar's Island, Tor Books. ISBN 978-0-7653-7452-3</li>
			<li>Tineke Bolleman. (2019). Trailblazer's Bounty. Paizo Inc.</li>
		  </list>
		</text>
	</license>
	<reference static="true">
		<equipment>
			<category name="Alcohols of Golarion" baseicon="0" decalicon="0">
				<id-00001>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Both red and white wine are produced in Cheliax including wine of the highest quality. Varian Jeggare owns vineyards in western Cheliax that produce both red and white wine. Notably fine Chelish wines include Wiscrani Barbera wine.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Wiscrani Barbera</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00001>
				<id-00002>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Urglin gin is an extremely potent gin said to overwhelm most humans after just one cup. It has many uses, such as for cleaning wounds, starting fires, or as an explosive agent.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Urglin Gin</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00002>
				<id-00003>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Collected by connoisseurs, this strong alcohol is made in Taldor.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Taldan Fire-Brandy</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00003>
				<id-00004>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Sealord wine is a generic term for wines, red and white, grown in coastal vineyards. The distinctive taste is favoured by nobles.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Sealord Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00004>
				<id-00005>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Extraction of the sap of palm trees may be performed by tapping the trees' trunks and this sap may then be fermented into palm wine.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Palm Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00005>
				<id-00006>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This variety of whiskey is a single-malt variety that has been made for nearly two hundred years targeted at the soldier community.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Oldlaw Whiskey</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00006>
				<id-00007>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Old Erebus is a cheap whiskey sold in brown bottles that is made in southern Cheliax.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Old Erebus</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00007>
				<id-00008>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Mupute is a strong pineapple liqueur distilled in Garund.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Mupute</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00008>
				<id-00009>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Extraction of the sap of palm trees may be performed by tapping the trees' trunks and this sap may then be fermented into palm wine. Sometimes, this palm wine may be distilled into a stronger drink called lagmi.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Lagmi Liquor</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00009>
				<id-00010>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This is the house rum at the Formidably Maid that is frighteningly strong. A keg is worth about 75 gp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Kill-Devil Rum</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00010>
				<id-00011>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p></p>
					</description>
					<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Honey Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00011>
				<id-00012>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Gin is a broad family of distilled spirits that all share juniper berries as a common ingredient. They are associated with the mysterious creatures known as ginevers, also called &quot;gin devils&quot;.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Gin</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00012>
				<id-00013>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Fish oil whiskey is a disgustingly smelling whiskey, sometimes taken for medicinal purposes.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Fish Oil Whiskey</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00013>
				<id-00014>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Both red and white wine are produced in Cheliax including wine of the highest quality. Varian Jeggare owns vineyards in western Cheliax that produce both red and white wine.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Chelish Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00014>
				<id-00015>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Bagog's liquor is a highly intoxicating still made by the owner of the Bagog's Roundhouse tavern in the town of Dragonsthrall on the Dahak's Horn island in the Shackles.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Bagog's Liquor</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00015>
				<id-00016>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Arrack is a distilled alcoholic spirit made from the fermented sap of coconut flowers, sugar cane, grain (e.g., red rice) or fruit. It is known to be popular in Elidir where a strong flavoured version is offered.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Arrack</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00016>
				<id-00017>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Beer from Andoran is highly prized by locals and lauded above other Inner Sea region beers.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Andoren Beer</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00017>
				<id-00018>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>An ale brewed at the Blackpeak Brewery in Dalaston.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Blackpeak Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00018>
				<id-00019>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Available in Andoran.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Barley Stout</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00019>
				<id-00020>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A dark ale served by Skogg Bloodhammer in his alehouse, The Cracked Anvil Brewery. It is rumored to make changes to the bodies of those who drink it that fade over time.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Bloodhammer Reserve</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00020>
				<id-00021>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Brow Brew is an oddity of beers, being produced primarily from grapes harvested from the vineyard of the Numerian town of Iadenveigh. The tough grapes are practically inedible, but are fermented with a particular yeast, grain and wood mushrooms to make a distinctive and rough beer considered an 'acquired taste' by visitors to the town.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Brow Brew</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00021>
				<id-00022>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Hardroot cider is known for being particularly dry.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Hardroot Cider</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00022>
				<id-00023>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A brew from the city of Magnimar, named after its primary fortification, Fort Indros.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Fort Indros Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00023>
				<id-00024>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Cheerful Delver Stout is a dark ale with an earthy character that has become quite well known and popular in Varnhold, and its immediate environs, since the town's small brewery was established.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Cheerful Delver Stout</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00024>
				<id-00025>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Dwarves have an ancient heritage of brewing strong ales since before the Quest for Sky. The potent liquors brewed in those early times with ingredients from the Darklands are approximated today by blending exotic ingredients with traditional grains and hops. In some cases, these special dwarven brews begin to take on characteristics akin to magic potions, though still crafted using alchemical methods; these are the dwarven magic ales, including.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Dwarven Magic Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00025>
				<id-00026>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Boulderhead Bock is a malty ale known for a thick and creamy froth. The additional effect of this brew is to numb pain.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Boulderhead Bock</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00026>
				<id-00027>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This disgusting concoction is made by adding toxin from a poisonous toad or frog to beer. The poison is inserted in different ways, such as soaking the amphibian in the ale, soaking its eggs in the ale or milking the poison from the amphibian and then mixing it in. Bufo is not consumed in civilized societies, but goblins, boggards and other primitive humanoids lap it up, sometimes eating the amphibian as a bonus at the end of their drink.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Bufo</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00027>
				<id-00028>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Found in the Osirian city of Ipeq, the local beer is a very filling beer that is sweet and thick in consistency.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Ipeq Beer</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00028>
				<id-00029>
					<cost type="string">4 sp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A salty, frothy, and pale beer, most races consider it too salty. At 4sp a mug, or 1 gp a gallon, it is not the cheapest beer in the tavern.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Luglurch Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00029>
				<id-00030>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Created by Zokar Elkarid of the Laughing Demon tavern in Ravengro, Ustalav, Liquid Ghosts is a pale ale, sweet to taste and strangely glowing with a greenish hue.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Liquid Ghosts</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00030>
				<id-00031>
					<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A cheap favorite of the unlucky of Ilizmagorti, it is made from the leftover dregs of whatever other drinks the bartender has made recently. It costs only 1cp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Bilgwater Surprize</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00031>
				<id-00032>
					<cost type="string">6 sp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>White Wine and pomegranate juice. This drink costs 6 sp each.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Damsel in Distress</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00032>
				<id-00033>
					<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Costing 2 sp, this cocktail is made from ginger beer, dark rum, and a slice of lime.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Dark and Stormy</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00033>
				<id-00034>
					<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Made by mixing dark rum, orange liqueur, and apple juice. In Ilizmagorti this drink costs 5 sp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Half a Doubloon</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00034>
				<id-00035>
					<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A drink sold to visitors to Ilizmagorti, this drink is made with absinthe and fruit. The absinthe and strong alcohol make the visitor a easy target for locals. Because of this, it costs 1 gp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Island Dream</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00035>
				<id-00036>
					<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A spicy drink, made from vodka, tomatoes, pepper, and some other vegetables. Legend states that the additional secret ingredient is blood of a fiendish giant praying mantis. A glass costs 1 gp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Kiss of the Mantis</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00036>
				<id-00037>
					<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Lisken's Medicinal Tonic is normally used as a relief for insomnia or as a gentle sedative but, for 10 gp per cup, halflings will purchase this alcoholic drink to slow and quieten themselves down in a more pronounced fashion; it has no such strong effect on other races.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Lisken's Medicinal Tonic</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00037>
				<id-00038>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This strong cocktail is served warm and contains rum, wine, ale, eggs, sugar and spices.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Rumboozle</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00038>
				<id-00039>
					<cost type="string">8 cp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Herb liqueur mixed with whiskey and honey from Ilizmagorti. A rusty cutlass costs 8 cp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Rusty Cutlass</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00039>
				<id-00040>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Made of cranberry and grapefruit juices, pomegranate extract, juniper gin, and a secret ingredient, this drink is said to improve its imbiber's chances for love when paired with a kiss of the lips on the mostly buried Whispering Stone statue in Wati. It is named for the tavern's owner, Teht Blackblossom.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Teht's Love Potion</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00040>
				<id-00041>
					<cost type="string">4 sp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A drink served in a glass with a salted rim, a three salts and a dog consists of Whiskey, brandy, tequila, rum and costs 4 sp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Three Salts and a Dog</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00041>
				<id-00042>
					<cost type="string">6 cp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Served similarly to three salts and a dog, a three sheets is made by mixing at least three different types of rum and costs 6 cp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Three Sheets</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00042>
				<id-00043>
					<cost type="string">1 sp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Costing a silver piece, a whore's breakfast is a mug of ale with a shot of rum dropped in it. This is topped off with a tomato wedge garnish.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Whore's Breakfast</name>
					<subtype type="string">Mixed Drinks</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00043>
				<id-00044>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Absinthe is a favoured drink of creative folk such as artists. It is green in colour and made from wormwood. Elven absinthe is also popular.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Absinthe</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00044>
				<id-00045>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Baijiu is a clear drink usually distilled from sorghum. Its taste is corrosive and has to be acquired.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Baijiu</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00045>
				<id-00046>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This strong liquor is served at the Lean-To tavern in the Varisian town of Wartle. It has a gritty consistency and the dregs may be partaken from the communal bottle, although this is not recommended.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Bog Grog</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00046>
				<id-00047>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Pesh brandy is a spirit presumably based on the drug pesh; it has a sweetness as well as a warmth on the palate.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Pesh Brandy</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00047>
				<id-00048>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Wine is produced in the Taldan city of Zimar.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Zimaran Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00048>
				<id-00049>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Ustalavic brandy may be very fine indeed.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Ustalavic Brandy</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00049>
				<id-00050>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Corn liquor is distilled liquor based on maize as its grain.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Corn Liquor</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00050>
				<id-00051>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This warming spirit is sold in The Hardened Road pub in Magnimar.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Daggermark Drip</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00051>
				<id-00052>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Gear grog is the house brew sold by Bruner Derwel in the Rusty Glove in Alkenstar; it is a thick oily spirit.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Gear Grog</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00052>
				<id-00053>
					<cost type="string">100 gp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A bottle of bloodberry gin can sell for as much as 100 gold pieces.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Bloodberry Gin</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00053>
				<id-00054>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Grain alcohol is made by distilling fermented grains of various types. Generic grain alcohol tends to be inferior to a whisky and can be used to spike drinks of a lower alcoholic content, such as ale.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Grain Alcohol</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00054>
				<id-00055>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Mulue is a fruit flourishing in the Mwangi Expanse growing on vines exclusively found almost a week into the jungle. The higher echelons of Chelish society ferment mulue to create a potent drink.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Mulue</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00055>
				<id-00056>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This Vudrani drink is made from fruit and is sweet and strongly alcoholic.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Penj</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00056>
				<id-00057>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Poitin is a potent potato liquor favored by leprechauns. The drink has magical properties, allowing mortals to see fey and other denizens of the First World free of illusions and plainly visible for an hour after drinking. This inevitably attracts the ire of hostile fey, much to the leprechauns' delight. It is also exceptionally strong, and those who drink of it rarely remember their experiences.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Poitin</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00057>
				<id-00058>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Rum is doled out on board many ships, sometimes diluted with water to make 'grog'. On many ships, the rum or grog ration is enforced and penalties are suffered for defaulting. Sometimes lemon or lime juice is added to the grog to prevent scurvy and to make the sometimes disgusting concoction more palatable. When rum is unavailable, grogs may be made by mixing whatever alcohol is available; even though it may be unpalatable, if it is all that is available, it will be drunk on board ship.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Rum (or Grog)</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00058>
				<id-00059>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This spirit, sold aflame, is two parts kill-devil rum, and one part gunpowder. It is sold at the Formidably Maid on Port Peril's dockside.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Fire in the Hole</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00059>
				<id-00060>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This grog is mixed with a raw siren's egg and sold at the Formidably Maid.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Salt-Licked Grog</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00060>
				<id-00061>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Rum may be flavoured with various spices to make spiced rum or spiced grog. One such recipe for spiced grog is a mixture of rum, spices, and some lime and sugar.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Spiced Rum (or Spiced Grog)</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00061>
				<id-00062>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This strong rum is made at the Two Knight Brewery in the Varisian town of Sandpoint.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Two Knight Brewery Rum</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00062>
				<id-00063>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This vodka is made from potatoes. One of the more famous varieties is served at the Tin King Alley Tavern in the Irriseni settlement of Zlatomesto.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Potato Vodka</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00063>
				<id-00064>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Whisky, sometimes spelt whiskey, is made in many varieties in many parts of Golarion. In essence, a whisky is distilled grain liquor. The grain might be barley, maize, rye or wheat. Ageing in wooden casks improves the flavour.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Whisky</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00064>
				<id-00065>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Black Hill Whiskey is a popular drink at the Copper Coin tavern in Torch, Numeria.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Black Hill Whiskey</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00065>
				<id-00066>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Sold by the bottle at Jeggare's Jug, the first drinking establishment built in Korvosa.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Chelaxian Pepper Whiskey / Chelish Pepper Whisky</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00066>
				<id-00067>
					<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>For 10 gp a cup, halflings tend to go on drinking binges of this dark liquor to conquer their fears. Supposedly, the creator accosted a dragon without weapons, and that is where the title went.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Dragon Punch Whiskey</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00067>
				<id-00068>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Dragonscar Whisky</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00068>
				<id-00069>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Whiskey made by gnomes is distinctive enough to distinguished.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Gnome Whiskey</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00069>
				<id-00070>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Janderhoff whiskey is distilled in Janderhoff, presumably by the native dwarves.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Janderhoff Whiskey</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00070>
				<id-00071>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A very potent whisky, throatburn is made by the gnomes of Kalsgard.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Throatburn</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00071>
				<id-00072>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Strong spirit distilled in the Lands of the Linnorm Kings. It is made in enough quantity for the barrels to be used for fuelling ring defences around villages called fire moats, burning with a blue flame. It is also used from flasks to clean wounds.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Vjarik</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00072>
				<id-00073>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Winteryew moonshine is the local liquor of the village of Waldsby in Irrisen made by distilling winteryew bark. It may be purchased, albeit in watered-down fashion, from the White Weasel, the only tavern in the village.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Winteryew Moonshine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Spirits)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00073>
				<id-00074>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p></p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Bellis Mead</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00074>
				<id-00075>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Cauim is made by chewing manioc root or maize creating a different type of beer.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Cauim</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00075>
				<id-00076>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>By repeatedly partially freezing this brew and removing the ice, the alcoholic content of Icecap Ale is forced up to ten times that of normal ale. This ale additionally boosts the strength and fortitude of the drinker but at a price of fatigue and memory loss greater than for a normal hangover.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Icecap Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00076>
				<id-00077>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Longbeard Lambic is an ancient recipe that can pull a drinker out of fatigue and fear.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Longbeard Lambic</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00077>
				<id-00078>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Wyrm's Breath Bitter is green-coloured, extremely fizzy and very bitter. Unfortunately, the ale causes nausea but as a secondary effect grants the imbiber a noxious belch acting similarly to a dragon's breath weapon. Those smelling the belch are sickened and deafened.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Wyrm's Breath Bitter</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00078>
				<id-00079>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Kumis is made by fermenting horse milk; it is drunk cold.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Kumis</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00079>
				<id-00080>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Mead comes in many different varieties but, in essence, it is fermented honey. Different varieties are flavoured with spices, fruit or hops. Regional meads can be found elsewhere in this article.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Mead</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00080>
				<id-00081>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>The arboreal regents of the Verduran Forest brew a concoction known as nodrim from fermented apples, wood chips, and clear water. It is intoxicating to them, but it is unknown whether it also similarly affects non-arboreal regents.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Nodrim</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00081>
				<id-00082>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Pulque is fermented using the heart or sap of agave plants forming a milky white, thick brew.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Pulque</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00082>
				<id-00083>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Qadiran cider may be found as far as Absalom.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Qadiran Cider</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00083>
				<id-00084>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Rusty Ale is a popular drink at the Copper Coin tavern in Torch, Numeria.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Rusty Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00084>
				<id-00085>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Sake is a strong alcoholic beverage brewed in a similar process to brewing beer; despite its manufacturing process, it is sometimes confusingly called rice wine outside Tian Xia. It is made in Tian Xia, particularly in Minkai. Sake may be aged, like wine, which increases its value. It is very rare to find sake in the Inner Sea region, though some is imported from Minkai.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Sake, or Rice Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00085>
				<id-00086>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Despite its fame as a centre for fine wine, some of the best ale and cider distributed in the Inner Sea region is brewed in Sarain in the River Kingdom of Pitax.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Sarain</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00086>
				<id-00087>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Steelforged Stout is a popular drink at the Copper Coin tavern in Torch, Numeria.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Steelforged Stout</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00087>
				<id-00088>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Tepache is a low-alcohol brew, found in tropical climes, that is made from beer, pineapple, sugar and cinnamon; sometimes other tropical fruits are used in place of the pineapple. The mixture is fermented together and the resulting brew is served cold with chilli powder.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Tepache</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00088>
				<id-00089>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Thileu bark is used to brew Thileu Lager sold by Jerikal Ashworth of Jerikal's Ales in Katapesh.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Thileu Lager</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00089>
				<id-00090>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Three Devil Ale is the house beer of the Silver Stoat tavern in the village of Heldren in Taldor. It is brewed on the premises by the landlady Kale Garimos and flavoured with hops imported from Cheliax, hence the ale's name, one assumes.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Three Devil Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00090>
				<id-00091>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This ale is known to be served in the Rusty Dragon inn in Sandpoint, Varisia and the Old Fang inn in Magnimar.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Ulseberry Ale</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00091>
				<id-00092>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Wineberry Mead is a popular drink at the Copper Coin tavern in Torch, Numeria.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Wineberry Mead</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Ale/Cider-Strength)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00092>
				<id-00093>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Alkenstar ice wine is a favoured among Geb's nobility but may also be found in the Rusty Glove in Alkenstar's Ferrous Quarter.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Alkenstar Ice Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00093>
				<id-00094>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Known to be drunk in Druma, this is a wine made from blackberries rather than grapes.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Blackberry Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00094>
				<id-00095>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Dessert wine is sweet wine taken during a sweet course of a meal.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Dessert Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00095>
				<id-00096>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Wine is produced in Druma and one of the more famous estates is owned by Kalistocrat Amynta Irel and located 15 miles west of Kerse. A particularly fine, and appropriately priced, example from the estate is called Encarthan Gold, named after the nearby Lake Encarthan. Even more expensive than Encarthan Gold, bottles of Encarthan Fishgold Rose are named after the unique red-coloured gold found only in the depths of Lake Encarthan.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Drumish Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00096>
				<id-00097>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Elven wine is very fine in quality and sweet in taste; it may even exceed a fine Galtan vintage wine in quality (see below). The alcoholic potency of the wine is often unrealized by those drinking it until much later. Elves of Kyonin also create subtle wines made from berries. Midsummer wine is made by the elves of Kyonin to celebrate the summer festival. It is a delicate white wine yet has a pleasing length.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Elven Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00097>
				<id-00098>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This wine may be aged to improve its quality and can be worth many gold pieces per bottle.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Galdurian Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00098>
				<id-00099>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Galtan wine can be very fine and smooth on the palate, though the revolutionary nature of the country currently makes wine making very difficult. Quality is sufficient enough that vintage wines may be made to lay down; these vintage wines may be sweet.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Galtan Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00099>
				<id-00100>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Irrisen Icewine from Hoarwood city may be purchased illegally from the White Weasel, the only tavern in the village of Waldsby in Irrisen.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Irrisen Icewine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00100>
				<id-00101>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Wine is produced in the Varisian city state of Korvosa, including port (q.v.).</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Korvosan Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00101>
				<id-00102>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Port is a fortified wine found in many varieties and hues, such as the tawny port of Korvosa.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Port</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00102>
				<id-00103>
					<cost type="string">200 gp</cost>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Sangwine is a dark red wine that smells of cedar and tastes of tannin and cocoa that retails at around 200 gold pieces for a bottle or close to 240 platinum pieces for a case. The wine is a favorite among the elite of Caliphas. The blood of someone who has recently drunk sangwine is embittered and it sickens creatures who feed on such blood, such as vampires.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Sangwine (bottle)</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00103>
				<id-00104>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Legends spread around Caliphas state that drinking wine of concordance with someone forms both a magical and emotional bond between the pair. This is a sweet white wine with notes of apple, lemon, and peach. It has the strongest citrus flavor of the wines created around Caliphas.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Wine of Concordance</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00104>
				<id-00105>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>A wine renowned as cheap and unpleasant from the village of Sauerton in Andoran.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Sauerton Red</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00105>
				<id-00106>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Stone giants have one exception to a policy of simple agriculture: viniculture. Stone giant wines are made for their own use and for their palate: they are sour and full of tannin, providing a dry and more bitter taste.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Stone Giant Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00106>
				<id-00107>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Syrinelle is a grape variety and is used to produce a fine elven vintage in the settlement of Riverspire in Kyonin.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Syrinelle</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00107>
				<id-00108>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Countess Carmilla Caliphvaso? has recently bought the neglected Iomedaean Abbey of Sante-Lymirin and its estate and turned it over vineyards and to producing wine. The wine is fine and marked as being of Countess Carmilla Caliphvaso?'s estate.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Ustalav Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00108>
				<id-00109>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>The monks of Whiterose Abbey used to be expert vintners (and brewers) blessed by Cayden Cailean such that their products gained in flavour and alcoholic strength. The abbey is found close to Mount Branthlend in the River Kingdoms. Wines known to have been produced include fine Whiterose chardonnay worth a fortune if sold today.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">0</locked>
					<name type="string">Whiterose Abbey Wine</name>
					<subtype type="string">Food and Drink (Wines)</subtype>
					<type type="string">Good and Services</type>
				</id-00109>
			</category>
		</equipment>
	</reference>
</root>
