<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="1|3.5E:17|CoreRPG:4">
	<library>
		<alcoholsofgolarion static="true">
			<categoryname type="string">Items</categoryname>
			<name type="string">alcoholsofgolarion</name>
			<entries>
				<aacommunity>
				  <librarylink type="windowreference">
					<class>referencetext</class>
					<recordname>communityuse</recordname>
				  </librarylink>
				  <name type="string">Community Use Statement</name>
				</aacommunity>
				<ablicense>
				  <librarylink type="windowreference">
					<class>referencetext</class>
					<recordname>license</recordname>
				  </librarylink>
				  <name type="string">Open Gaming License</name>
				</ablicense>
				<item>
					<librarylink type="windowreference">
						<class>reference_list</class>
						<recordname>..</recordname>
					</librarylink>
					<name type="string">Alcohols</name>
					<recordtype type="string">item</recordtype>
				</item>
			</entries>
		</alcoholsofgolarion>
	</library>
	<communityuse>
		<name type="string">Community Use Statement</name>
		<text type="formattedtext">
		  <p>This<i>Fantasy Grounds Module</i> uses trademarks and/or copyrights owned by Paizo Publishing, LLC, which are used under Paizo's Community Use Policy. We are expressly prohibited from charging you to use or access this content. This<i>Fantasy Grounds Module</i> is not published, endorsed, or specifically approved by Paizo Publishing. For more information about Paizo's Community Use Policy, please visit paizo.com/communityuse. For more information about Paizo Publishing and Paizo products, please visit paizo.com.</p>
		</text>
	</communityuse>
	<license>
		<librarylink type="windowreference">
		  <class>referencetextwide</class>
		  <recordname>..</recordname>
		</librarylink>
		<name type="string">Open Gaming License</name>
		<text type="formattedtext">
		  <p>
			<b>Open Game License Version 1.0a</b>
		  </p>
		  <p>The following text is the property of Wizards of the Coast, Inc. and is Copyright 2000 Wizards of the Coast, Inc ("Wizards"). All Rights Reserved.</p>
		  <p>1. Definitions:</p>
		  <list>
			<li>(a) "Contributors" means the copyright and/or trademark owners who have contributed Open Game Content;</li>
			<li>(b) "Derivative Material" means copyrighted material including derivative works and translations (including into other computer languages), potation, modification, correction, addition, extension, upgrade, improvement, compilation, abridgment or other form in which an existing work may be recast, transformed or adapted;</li>
			<li>(c) "Distribute" means to reproduce, license, rent, lease, sell, broadcast, publicly display, transmit or otherwise distribute;</li>
			<li>(d) "Open Game Content" means the game mechanic and includes the methods, procedures, processes and routines to the extent such content does not embody the Product Identity and is an enhancement over the prior art and any additional content clearly identified as Open Game Content by the Contributor, and means any work covered by this License, including translations and derivative works under copyright law, but specifically excludes Product Identity.</li>
			<li>(e) "Product Identity" means product and product line names, logos and identifying marks including trade dress; artifacts, creatures, characters, stories, storylines, plots, thematic elements, dialogue, incidents, language, artwork, symbols, designs, depictions, likenesses, formats, poses, concepts, themes and graphic, photographic and other visual or audio representations; names and descriptions of characters, spells, enchantments, personalities, teams, personas, likenesses and special abilities; places, locations, environments, creatures, equipment, magical or supernatural abilities or effects, logos, symbols, or graphic designs; and any other trademark or registered trademark clearly identified as Product identity by the owner of the Product Identity, and which specifically excludes the Open Game Content;</li>
			<li>(f) "Trademark" means the logos, names, mark, sign, motto, designs that are used by a Contributor to identify itself or its products or the associated products contributed to the Open Game License by the Contributor</li>
			<li>(g) "Use", "Used" or "Using" means to use, Distribute, copy, edit, format, modify, translate and otherwise create Derivative Material of Open Game Content.</li>
			<li>(h) "You" or "Your" means the licensee in terms of this agreement.</li>
		  </list>
		  <p>2. The License: This License applies to any Open Game Content that contains a notice indicating that the Open Game Content may only be Used under and in terms of this License. You must affix such a notice to any Open Game Content that you Use. No terms may be added to or subtracted from this License except as described by the License itself. No other terms or conditions may be applied to any Open Game Content distributed using this License.</p>
		  <p>3. Offer and Acceptance: By Using the Open Game Content You indicate Your acceptance of the terms of this License.</p>
		  <p>4. Grant and Consideration: In consideration for agreeing to use this License, the Contributors grant You a perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free, non-exclusive license with the exact terms of this License to Use, the Open Game Content.</p>
		  <p>5. Representation of Authority to Contribute: If You are contributing original material as Open Game Content, You represent that Your Contributions are Your original creation and/or You have sufficient rights to grant the rights conveyed by this License.</p>
		  <p>6. Notice of License Copyright: You must update the COPYRIGHT NOTICE portion of this License to include the exact text of the COPYRIGHT NOTICE of any Open Game Content You are copying, modifying or distributing, and You must add the title, the copyright date, and the copyright holder's name to the COPYRIGHT NOTICE of any original Open Game Content you Distribute.</p>
		  <p>7. Use of Product Identity: You agree not to Use any Product Identity, including as an indication as to compatibility, except as expressly licensed in another, independent Agreement with the owner of each element of that Product Identity. You agree not to indicate compatibility or co-adaptability with any Trademark or Registered Trademark in conjunction with a work containing Open Game Content except as expressly licensed in another, independent Agreement with the owner of such Trademark or Registered Trademark. The use of any Product Identity in Open Game Content does not constitute a challenge to the ownership of that Product Identity. The owner of any Product Identity used in Open Game Content shall retain all rights, title and interest in and to that Product Identity.</p>
		  <p>8. Identification: If you distribute Open Game Content You must clearly indicate which portions of the work that you are distributing are Open Game Content.</p>
		  <p>9. Updating the License: Wizards or its designated Agents may publish updated versions of this License. You may use any authorized version of this License to copy, modify and distribute any Open Game Content originally distributed under any version of this License.</p>
		  <p>10. Copy of this License: You MUST include a copy of this License with every copy of the Open Game Content You distribute.</p>
		  <p>11. Use of Contributor Credits: You may not market or advertise the Open Game Content using the name of any Contributor unless You have written permission from the Contributor to do so.</p>
		  <p>12. Inability to Comply: If it is impossible for You to comply with any of the terms of this License with respect to some or all of the Open Game Content due to statute, judicial order, or governmental regulation then You may not Use any Open Game Material so affected.</p>
		  <p>13. Termination: This License will terminate automatically if You fail to comply with all terms herein and fail to cure such breach within 30 days of becoming aware of the breach. All sublicenses shall survive the termination of this License.</p>
		  <p>14. Reformation: If any provision of this License is held to be unenforceable, such provision shall be reformed only to the extent necessary to make it enforceable.</p>
		  <p>
			<b>15. COPYRIGHT NOTICE</b>
		  </p>
		  <p>
			<i>Open Game License v 1.0a Copyright 2000, Wizards of the Coast, Inc.</i>
		  </p>
		  <list>
			<li>System Reference Document. Copyright 2000, Wizards of the Coast, Inc.; Authors Jonathan Tweet, Monte Cook, Skip Williams, based on material by E. Gary Gygax and Dave Arneson.</li>
			<li>F. Wesley Schneider. (2016). "The Hellfire Compact". Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-818-2</li>
			<li>Tineke Bolleman. (2019). Trailblazer's Bounty. Paizo Inc.</li>
			<li>Neil Spicer. (2010). Blood for Blood. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-251-7</li>
			<li>Jason Bulmahn et al. (2012). Ultimate Equipment. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-390-3</li>
			<li>Richard Pett. (2014). Tephu, City of the Reed People. Shifting Sands. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-60125-590-7</li>
			<li>Dave Gross. (2011). "A Lesson in Taxonomy". Paizo Publishing. ISBN 978-1-60125-394-1 </li>
			<li>Kate Baker, Eleanor Ferron, Michelle Jones, Jason Keeley, Luis Loza, Jacob W. Michaels, Joe Pasini, and David N. Ross. (2018). Inner Sea Taverns. Paizo Inc. ISBN 978-1-64078-016-3</li>
			<li>Mike Shel. (2012). Isles of the Shackles. Paizo Publishing, LLC. ISBN 978-1-60125-408-5</li>
			<li>Chris A. Jackson. (2013). "Stargazer", Paizo Publishing.</li>
			<li>Hugh Matthews. (2012). "Krunzle the Quick". Paizo Publishing.</li>
		  </list>
		</text>
	</license>
	<reference static="true">
		<equipment>
			<category name="Alcohols of Golarion" baseicon="0" decalicon="0">
				<id-00001>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Both red and white wine are produced in Cheliax including wine of the highest quality. Varian Jeggare owns vineyards in western Cheliax that produce both red and white wine. Notably fine Chelish wines include Wiscrani Barbera wine.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Wiscrani Barbera</name>
				</id-00001>
				<id-00002>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Urglin gin is an extremely potent gin said to overwhelm most humans after just one cup. It has many uses, such as for cleaning wounds, starting fires, or as an explosive agent.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Urglin gin</name>
				</id-00002>
				<id-00003>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Collected by connoisseurs, this strong alcohol is made in Taldor.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Taldan Fire-Brandy</name>
				</id-00003>
				<id-00004>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Sealord wine is a generic term for wines, red and white, grown in coastal vineyards. The distinctive taste is favoured by nobles.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Sealord Wine</name>
				</id-00004>
				<id-00005>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Extraction of the sap of palm trees may be performed by tapping the trees' trunks and this sap may then be fermented into palm wine.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Palm Wine</name>
				</id-00005>
				<id-00006>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This variety of whiskey is a single-malt variety that has been made for nearly two hundred years targeted at the soldier community.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Oldlaw Whiskey</name>
				</id-00006>
				<id-00007>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Old Erebus is a cheap whiskey sold in brown bottles that is made in southern Cheliax.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Old Erebus</name>
				</id-00007>
				<id-00008>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Mupute is a strong pineapple liqueur distilled in Garund.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Mupute</name>
				</id-00008>
				<id-00009>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Extraction of the sap of palm trees may be performed by tapping the trees' trunks and this sap may then be fermented into palm wine. Sometimes, this palm wine may be distilled into a stronger drink called lagmi.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Lagmi Liquor</name>
				</id-00009>
				<id-00010>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>This is the house rum at the Formidably Maid that is frighteningly strong. A keg is worth about 75 gp.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Kill-devil rum</name>
				</id-00010>
				<id-00011>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p></p>
					</description>
					<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Honey wine</name>
				</id-00011>
				<id-00012>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Gin is a broad family of distilled spirits that all share juniper berries as a common ingredient. They are associated with the mysterious creatures known as ginevers, also called &quot;gin devils&quot;.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Gin</name>
				</id-00012>
				<id-00013>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Fish oil whiskey is a disgustingly smelling whiskey, sometimes taken for medicinal purposes.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Fish Oil Whiskey</name>
				</id-00013>
				<id-00014>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Both red and white wine are produced in Cheliax including wine of the highest quality. Varian Jeggare owns vineyards in western Cheliax that produce both red and white wine.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Chelish Wine</name>
				</id-00014>
				<id-00015>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Bagog's liquor is a highly intoxicating still made by the owner of the Bagog's Roundhouse tavern in the town of Dragonsthrall on the Dahak's Horn island in the Shackles.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Bagog's liquor</name>
				</id-00015>
				<id-00016>
					<description type="formattedtext">
						<p>Arrack is a distilled alcoholic spirit made from the fermented sap of coconut flowers, sugar cane, grain (e.g., red rice) or fruit. It is known to be popular in Elidir where a strong flavoured version is offered.</p>
					</description>
					<locked type="number">1</locked>
					<name type="string">Arrack</name>
				</id-00016>
			</category>
		</equipment>
	</reference>
</root>
